<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="attitue">
        <item>I\'m not changed it\’s just I grew up and you should try too.</item>
        <item>I never insult people I only tell them what they are. </item>
        <item>If you think I am BAD than you’re wrong, I\'m the worst. </item>
        <item>The biggest slap to your enemies is your success.</item>
        <item>I always arrive late at office but I make it by leaving early. </item>
        <item>I\’m sorry my fault. I forgot you’re an Idiot</item>
        <item>I don\’t have a bad handwriting, I have my own FONT.</item>
        <item>My attitude based on how you treat me. </item>
        <item>Hakuna Matata!!! – The great motto to live life... </item>
        <item>Yeah You - The one reading my status, Get Lost! </item>
        <item>When a bird hits your window have you ever wondered if God is playing angry birds with you? </item>
        <item>I know the voices in my head aren\’t real but sometimes their ideas are just absolutely awesome!</item>
        <item>I loved a girl and she broke my heart. Now every piece of my heart love different girls. People called it flirt that\'s not fair…</item>
        <item>Dear Mario, I wasted my childhood trying to save your girlfriend. Now, you help me to save mine.</item>
        <item>Childhood is like being drunk, everyone remembers what you did, except you.</item>
        <item>I\’m poor. I can’t pay attention in class room. </item>
        <item>When I\'m good I\'m best , when I\'m bad I\'m worst. </item>
        <item>I\’m cool but global warming made me hot. </item>
        <item> Excuse me. I found something under my shoes oh its your Attitude</item>
        <item>If people are trying to bring you \‘Down\’, It only means that you are \‘Above them\’. </item>
        <item>Please don\’t get confused between my personality and my attitude. </item>
        <item>I\'m Not Special , I\'m Just Limited Edition.</item>
        <item>Everything that kills me makes me feel alive.</item>
        <item> I enjoy when people show Attitude to me because it shows that they need an Attitude to impress me! </item>
        <item>Stop checking my status ! Go get a Life! </item>
        <item>Coins always make sound but the currency notes are always silent! that\’s why I\’m always calm and silent.</item>
        <item>Life is too short. Don\'t waste it removing pen drive safely.</item>
        <item>Life will give you exactly what you need, not what you want.</item>
        <item>I did lots of stupid things on social networking sites but atleast I never commented \“Cute pic dear\“ on girls profile picture. </item>
        <item>I started out with nothing and i still have most of it </item>
        <item> I will marry the girl who look as pretty as in her Aadhaar card </item>
        <item>They say we learn from our mistakes. So I\'m making as many as possible! Soon I will be a genius.</item>
        <item>Sorry vegetarians we can\’t pretend.</item>
        <item>Life is too short. Don\’t waste it reading my Whatsapp status.</item>
        <item>Tried to loose weight… But it keeps finding me.</item>
        <item> I just saved a bunch of money on my car insurance by selling my car. </item>
        <item> lazy People Fact #5812672793 You were too lazy to read that number. </item>
        <item>If your bad. Call me your Dad. </item>
        <item>What is a Best friend? A single soul in two bodies. </item>
        <item> I don\'t have an attitude, I have standards for the people who are supposed to be my friends. </item>
        <item>It is better to live alone. There is no friendship with a fool. </item>
        <item> Fake friends believe in rumors. Real friends believe in you. </item>
        <item> Never forget who was there for you when no one else was. </item>
        <item> I love to walk in fog, because nobody knows I\'m smoking. </item>
        <item>I\'m not drunk, I\'m just chemically off-balanced</item>
        <item>Oh, so you wanna argue, bring it. I got my CAPS LOCK ON. </item>
        <item>I\'m so poor that I can\'t pay attention in class.</item>
        <item>Warning!!! I know KARATE and few other oriental words. </item>
        <item> I\'m not virgin, my life fucks me everyday.</item>
        <item> I talk to myself because I like dealing with a better class of people. </item>
        <item> Save water drink beer. </item>
        <item>Not all men are fools, some stay bachelor.</item>
        <item>Phones are better than girlfriends, at least we can switch off.</item>
        <item>I love my job only when I\'m on vacation </item>
        <item>Friends come and go, but enemies remain and build up. </item>
        <item>Behind every successful man is a surprised woman. </item>
        <item>Some people call me Mike, you can call me tonight. </item>
        <item>Sometimes you succeed and other times you learn. </item>
        <item> Not always \"Available\".. try your Luck.. </item>
        <item>Time is precious, waste it wisely. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>