<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="friendship">
        <item>A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out</item>
        <item>If you live to be 100, I hope I live to be 100 minus 1 day, so I never have to live without you</item>
        <item>I like to listen. I have learned a great deal from listening carefully. Most people never listen</item>
        <item>Friendship is born at that moment when one person says to another, \‘What! You too? I thought I was the only one</item>
        <item>True friendship comes when the silence between two people is comfortable</item>
        <item>Sweet is the memory of distant friends! Like the mellow rays of the departing sun, it falls tenderly, yet sadly, on the heart</item>
        <item>There\’s not a word yet for old friends who\’ve just met</item>
        <item>A single rose can be my garden… a single friend, my world</item>
        <item>Don\’t make friends who are comfortable to be with. Make friends who will force you to lever yourself up</item>
        <item>You can make more friends in two months by becoming interested in other people than you can in two years by trying to get other people interested in you.</item>
        <item>A friend is someone who understands your past, believes in your future, and accepts you just the way you are</item>
        <item>Ultimately the bond of all companionship, whether in marriage or in friendship, is conversation</item>
        <item>A true friend never gets in your way unless you happen to be going down.</item>
        <item>I don\’t need a friend who changes when I change and who nods when I nod; my shadow does that much better</item>
        <item>The real test of friendship is can you literally do nothing with the other person? Can you enjoy those moments of life that are utterly simple?</item>
        <item>A loyal friend laughs at your jokes when they\’re not so good, and sympathizes with your problems when they\’re not so bad</item>
        <item>It is not a lack of love, but a lack of friendship that makes unhappy marriages.</item>
        <item>Friendship is the hardest thing in the world to explain. It\’s not something you learn in school. But if you haven\’t learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven\’t learned anything</item>
        <item>Growing apart doesn\’t change the fact that for a long time we grew side by side; our roots will always be tangled. I\’m glad for that</item>
        <item>One\’s friends are that part of the human race with which one can be human</item>
        <item>For beautiful eyes, look for the good in others; for beautiful lips, speak only words of kindness; and for poise, walk with the knowledge that you are never alone</item>
        <item>Be slow to fall into friendship; but when thou art in, continue firm and constant</item>
        <item>One measure of friendship consists not in the number of things friends can discuss, but in the number of things they need no longer mention.</item>
        <item>Tis the privilege of friendship to talk nonsense, and to have her nonsense respected.</item>
        <item>Let us be grateful to the people who make us happy; they are the charming gardeners who make our souls blossom</item>
        <item>If you go looking for a friend, you\’re going to find they\’re very scarce. If you go out to be a friend, you\’ll find them everywhere</item>
        <item>In the End, we will remember not the words of our enemies, but the silence of our friends</item>
        <item>Keep away from those who try to belittle your ambitions. Small people always do that, but the really great make you believe that you too can become great</item>
        <item>No person is your friend who demands your silence, or denies your right to grow</item>
        <item>Friendship is the only cement that will ever hold the world together</item>
        <item>Friends are those rare people who ask how we are and then wait to hear the answer</item>


    </string-array>
</resources>