<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="funny"
        formatted="false">
        <item>My damn phone doesn\’t allow me text or call due to low battery but it has enough battery to keep screaming, “Low battery, Low battery</item>
        <item>I\’m pretty sure the whole \“ladies first\” thing was created by a guy just to check out ass.</item>
        <item>Hmmmm…..Don\’t copy my status.</item>
        <item>80% of boys have girlfriends.. Rest 20% are having brain.</item>
        <item>Never laugh at your wife\’s choices… you’re one of them</item>
        <item>Am gonna Make my Status………….better you too Focus on your Status only</item>
        <item>I wonder what happens when doctor\’s wife eats an apple a day</item>
        <item>The only time success comes before work is in dictionary.</item>
        <item>I have enough money to last me the rest of my life, unless I buy something.</item>
        <item>I always dream of being a millionaire like my uncle!… He’s dreaming too.</item>
        <item>At least mosquito\’s are attracted to me.</item>
        <item>Don\’t kiss behind the garden, Love is blind but the neighbors are not.</item>
        <item>God is really creative , i mean ..just look at me</item>
        <item>Everything funnier when your supposed to be quiet..</item>
        <item>I live in a world of fantasy, so keep your reality away from me!</item>
        <item>You can never buy Love….But still you have to pay for it ..</item>
        <item>Life is Short – Chat Fast!</item>
        <item>Totally available!! Please disturb me!!</item>
        <item>My wife dresses to kill. She cooks the same way.</item>
        <item>Sometimes all you need is love. Lol, just kidding, you need money.</item>
        <item>If you can\’t convince her then confuse her</item>
        <item>Whenever I think of quit smoking, I need a cigarette</item>
        <item>I wish there was a day between Saturday and Sunday.</item>
        <item>I talk to myself often that way I ensure I am talking to better class of people.</item>
        <item>There\’s only one problem with your face, I can see it.</item>
        <item>I pretend to work. They pretend to pay me.</item>
        <item>Behind every great man, there is a surprised woman.</item>
        <item>Looks like I over-estimated the number of your brain cells.</item>
        <item>A man is as young as the woman he feels.</item>
        <item>If people are talking behind your back, then just fart.</item>
        <item>I am Cool but Summer Days make me hot..</item>
        <item>I am not failed, Because my success is lost.!</item>
        <item>Love is like fart. If you force it, It\’s probably shit.</item>
        <item>I\’m not sarcastic, I am just intelligent beyond your understanding.</item>
        <item>My ex had one very annoying habit – BREATHING</item>
        <item>Some people are beautifully wrapped boxes of shit.</item>
        <item>Whatsapp users never die, they just go offline.</item>
        <item>I told cashier- I want to open a joint account with anyone who have lots of money.</item>
        <item>A fine is a tax for doing wrong. A tax is a fine for doing well.</item>
        <item>I just need a good Wifi and Wife.</item>
        <item>Hello madam, do you want Credit Card? Girl: No thanks, I have a Boyfriend.</item>
        <item>Worrying works! 90% of the things I worry about never happen.</item>
        <item>Just remember…if the world didn’t suck, we’d all fall off.</item>
        <item>No, I’m not feeling violent, I’m feeling creative with weapons.</item>
        <item>I may be fat, but you\’re ugly – I can lose weight!</item>
        <item>Knowledge is power, and power corrupts. So study hard and be evil.</item>
        <item>Girls are like roads, more the curves, more the dangerous they are.</item>
        <item>Why do women always ask questions that have no right answers?</item>
        <item>The winner of the rat race is still a rat.</item>
        <item>I\’m in shape. Round is a shape isn\’t it?</item>
        <item>Am fantaastic if I drink Fantaa.</item>
        <item>Cousins are created so that our Parents can compare marks.</item>
        <item>Mah Attitude.. Mah ishtyle !</item>
        <item>Don\’t browse my phone when I give it for viewing an image.</item>
        <item>Virginity is not dignity, It is just lack of opportunity</item>
        <item>I\'m the dude with cool attitude</item>
        <item>Yes I am smiling and you\'re not the reason anymore.</item>
        <item>Silence is the best response to a fool.</item>
        <item>A tear is made of 1% of water and 99% of feelings.</item>
        <item>It\'s not an attitude, it\'s the way I am.</item>
        <item>I don\'t have an attitude problem, I just have a personality that you can\'t handle.</item>
        <item>My life my rules.</item>
        <item>Don\'t judge me I was born to be awesome not perfect.</item>
        <item>I do not get drunk- I get awesome.</item>
        <item>Time is precious waste it wisely.</item>
        <item>Do not argue with an idiot, he will drag you down to his level and beat you with experience.</item>
        <item>A jealous woman does better research than FBI.</item>
        <item>Life is short. Smile while you still have teeth.</item>
        <item>Life is short. Smile while you still have teeth.</item>
        <item>The only reason I am fat because a tiny body couldn\'t store all this personality.</item>
        <item>Going to Macdonald for a salad is like going to prostitute for a hug.</item>
        <item>The best things in life are free, the second best are very expensive.</item>
        <item>I am not arguing, I\'m simply explaining why I am right.</item>
        <item>Some people need a HIGH-FIVE, in the face with a chair.</item>
        <item>Life is too short. Don\'t waste it reading my status...</item>
        <item>I am Waiting for GF Message!</item>
        <item>There comes a point in life, when you realize who really matters, who never did, and who always will..</item>
        <item>I miss the days when I was put my head on my desk...</item>
        <item>Always smiling, because your smile is a reason for many others to smile...Smile please...!!</item>
        <item>When you care about someone, their happiness matters more than yours.!!</item>
        <item>Sometimes you need to maintain a distance to keep them close to you..</item>
        <item>Good thing is listening a new song is that it doesn\'t remind you of anyone...</item>
        <item>Beauty is like Moon, looks much better at Night...</item>
        <item>Your looks don\'t make you Beautiful, it\'s the person inside who makes you beautiful..</item>
        <item>Someone asked me How is your life? I just smiled and replied, She is fine..</item>
        <item>I don\'t care what people think or say about me!..</item>
        <item>I am learn from My Mistake!Without Mistake We Can\'t Learn Best.</item>
        <item>There are two type of people winner and Losser,Winner always Working Hard,Losser Always try to shortcut for win.</item>
        <item>Try to solve your problem yourself... Don\'t Depend on other..!</item>
        <item>Every people is a intelligent, When he work Hard!</item>
        <item>Please don\'t get confused between my my attitude and personality!</item>
        <item>I\'m cool but Summer made me hot!</item>
        <item>Work until you don\'t have to, introduce yourself.</item>
        <item>Those who know love has also the risk of knowing pain.</item>
        <item>I want my Girlfriend like Google, She will understand me better.</item>
        <item>Every problem comes with solution, but my GF don\'t have.</item>
        <item>Dear Lord, there is a bug in your software... It\'s called #Sunday, please fix it !</item>
        <item>I Wish My Parents Were Like Google... They Should Understand Me Even Before I Complete...</item>
        <item>Every problem comes with some solution... If it doesn\'t have any solution, it\'s a Girl!</item>
        <item>I am not Spiderman Nor Superman However i am superhero for my GF.!</item>
        <item>WIFE and INSULT Are Somewhat Similar, They Always Look Good,IF IT IS NOT YOURS!</item>
        <item>In Love Story, Mom Agrees And Dad Disagrees? It\'s Because Mom Knows What Love Is, And Dad Knows What Boys Are...</item>
        <item>People say me bad.. but trust me I am the worst!</item>
        <item>There are three sides to an argument.. my side, your side and the right side.</item>
        <item>Phones are better than GF, At least we can switch it off...</item>
        <item>Totally available!! Please disturb me!!</item>
        <item>Whenever I find the key to success , someone changes the lock...</item>
        <item>Life is journey. I am traveler.</item>
        <item>Life must go on</item>
        <item>Never too busy to be happy</item>
        <item>Brains are awesome, I wish everyone had one.</item>
        <item>A smile suits every kind of clothes</item>
        <item>How come wrong numbers are never busy?</item>
        <item>Many a man owes his success to his first wife and his second wife to his success.</item>
        <item>The thing that impresses me the most about America is the way parents obey their children</item>
        <item>DRINK TRIPLE, SEE DOUBLE, ACT SINGLE.</item>
        <item>Teachers Only Teach The Rules... But Winners, Winners Make The Rules.</item>
        <item>My room + internet connection + music + food - homework = perfect day</item>
        <item>Live ♀, Laugh ☺, Love ♥</item>
        <item>Keep calm and enjoy life.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>