<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="lessons">
        <item>In this life, when you deny someone an apology, you will remember it at time you beg forgiveness.</item>
        <item>Short cuts make long delays.</item>
        <item>No matter how hard you kick, no matter how high you get, you can\'t go all the way around.</item>
        <item>But one of the big lessons I have learned from my journey is you can\'t please everyone, so don\'t try.   </item>
        <item>You can\'t wait around for something to become good, it either is, or isn\'t.</item>
        <item>I am not someone who is ashamed of my past. I\'m actually really proud. I know I made a lot of mistakes, but they, in turn, were my life lessons.</item>
        <item>Mistakes are a part of being human. Appreciate your mistakes for what they are: precious life lessons that can only be learned the hard way.  </item>
        <item>Your time is limited, so don\'t waste it living someone else\'s life.</item>
        <item>Life is inherently risky. There is only one big risk you should avoid at all costs, and that is the risk of doing nothing.</item>
        <item>You get in life what you have the courage to ask for.</item>
        <item>Life is not a problem to be solved, but a reality to be experienced.  </item>
        <item>A great attitude becomes a great day which becomes a great month which becomes a great year which becomes a great life.</item>
        <item>You can\'t live your life for other people. You\'ve got to do what\'s right for you, even if it hurts some people you love.</item>
        <item>Don\'t let anyone ever make you feel like you don\'t deserve what you want.</item>
        <item>We are who we choose to be.</item>
        <item>After a while, you learn to ignore the names people call you and just trust who you are.</item>
        <item>I didn\'t get there by wishing for it or hoping for it, but by working for it.   </item>
        <item>I can accept failure, everyone fails at something. But I cannot accept not trying.</item>
        <item>In every success story, you will find someone who has made a courageous decision.</item>
        <item>If there are things you don\'t like in the world you grew up in, make your own life different.   </item>
        <item>We make a living by what we get. We make a life by what we give.     </item>
        <item>In three words I can sum up everything I\'ve learned about life: it goes on.     </item>
        <item>The hardest thing to learn in life is which bridge to cross and which bridge to burn.</item>
        <item>Things turn out best for those who make the best of the way things turn out.</item>
        <item>Mistakes are part of the dues one pays for a full life.</item>
        <item>Good judgment comes from experience, and experience comes from bad judgment.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>