<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="love">
        <item> Where there is love there is life.</item>
        <item>Love is just love, it can never explained.</item>
        <item>Every time you texts me my cheeks hurt! I guess I smile too big.</item>
        <item>Every moment I spent with you.. is like beautiful dream come true</item>
        <item>Happiness is falling asleep next to you and waking up thinking I\’m still in my dreams.</item>
        <item>It feels so good to wake up with you in the morning.</item>
        <item> Someone has stolen my heart and you are the highest on my list of suspects.</item>
        <item>The first thing I imagined when I saw the word \‘love\’ is you</item>
        <item>Every time I see you I fall in love all over again</item>
        <item> You are the best thing that\’s ever been.</item>
        <item>Being someone\'s first love may be great, but to be their last is beyond perfect.</item>
        <item>Love is more than my live and my love is you.</item>
        <item>A successful relationship requires falling in love many times, always with the same person. </item>
        <item>Every love story is beautiful, but our is my favorite.</item>
        <item> Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage.</item>
        <item> Real happiness is when you marry a girl for love and find out later she has lots of money.</item>
        <item>Love means two minds without a single thought.</item>
        <item>Love is an ocean of emotions entirely surrounded by expenses</item>
        <item> When I dream, I dream of you. Maybe one day, dreams will come true. Because, I really love you.</item>
        <item>I love my life because it\’s you.</item>
        <item>Thinking of you is easy, I do it every day. Missing you is the heartache that never goes away..</item>
        <item>Nothing is fine, but when I\’m with you everything is fine.</item>
        <item>You\’re the ping to my pong. </item>
        <item>Love is like a baby, it needs to be treated gently.</item>
        <item>A life without love is like a year without summer. </item>
        <item>Love is like a rubber band you need to hold it from both the sides by two people. When one leaves it hurts.</item>
        <item>Say it before you run out of time. Say it before it\’s too late. Say what you\’re feeling. Waiting is a mistake.</item>
        <item>Girls want to find a superman but walk past Clark Kent every day. </item>
        <item>The madness of love is the greatest of heaven\’s blessings.</item>
        <item>Don\’t die with your song still inside of you. </item>
        <item>Don\’t look for love. Quietly give it away and let if find you back.</item>
        <item> I\’m in love with the idea of being in love. </item>
        <item> Sometimes following your heart means breaking someone else\'s </item>
        <item>Love means never having to say you\’re sorry.</item>
        <item>Getting over him sounds great but being in his arms sounds a lot better. </item>
        <item>Your smile is more beautiful than stars. </item>
        <item>If you are in love you can\’t get in comfort zone. </item>
        <item>The mind sets limits, the heart breaks them.</item>
        <item>The most beautiful line is But, I love you! </item>
        <item>You are just a memory of my love. </item>
        <item>My heart always will be yours.</item>
        <item> Stop falling in love with me. </item>
        <item>Distance doesn\’t matter in true love. </item>
        <item>You cannot buy Love, but still you need to pay for it. </item>
        <item>Everything is fine in Love and War. </item>
        <item>Be aware to touch me… you may be victim of Love. </item>
        <item>I\'’m in love with Whatsapp.</item>
        <item>I\'m not drunk, I\’m in love.</item>
        <item>When nothing goes right in Love... Go left! </item>
        <item> Silent people have the greatest heart.Love is in my Heart. </item>
        <item>Your smile is the key of my heart. </item>
        <item>Beautiful lies in face not in mind. </item>
        <item>When the angels ask what I most loved about life, I\’ll say you.</item>
        <item>Every time you texts me my cheeks hurt! I guess I smile too big.</item>
        <item>Never trust your heart because it\’s on the right side. </item>
        <item>Love isn\’t complicated, people are. </item>
        <item>Your cute smile is all I need to battle all struggles in my life.</item>
        <item>The best relationship is when you two can act like lovers and best friends.</item>
        <item>I promise you no one will ever love you like I do.</item>
        <item>You have no idea how fast my heart beats when I see you! </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>