<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="moti">
        <item>Dreams is not what you see in sleep is the thing which doesn\'t let you sleep</item>
        <item>Hard work beats talent when talent doesn\'t work hard.</item>
        <item>Life is about making an impact, not making an income.</item>
        <item>Do not give up the beginning is always the hardest.</item>
        <item>Whatever the mind of man can conceive and believe, it can achieve</item>
        <item>Strive not to be a success, but rather to be of value</item>
        <item>Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out</item>
        <item>I attribute my success to this: I never gave or took any excuse</item>
        <item>Success is going from failure to failure without losing your enthusiasm.</item>
        <item>The only way to do great work is to love what you do.</item>
        <item>If you are not willing to risk the usual, you will have to settle for the ordinary.</item>
        <item>"I haven\'t failed. I\'ve just found 10,000 ways that won\'t work.</item>
        <item>If you genuinely want something, don\’t wait for it. Teach yourself to be impatient." — Gurbaksh Chahal</item>
        <item>Dream big and dare to fail</item>
        <item>It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop.</item>
        <item>Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs</item>
        <item>Limitations live only in our minds. But if we use our imaginations, our possibilities become limitless</item>
        <item>Challenges are what make life interesting and overcoming them is what makes life meaningful</item>
        <item>Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears</item>
        <item>Happiness is not something readymade. It comes from your own actions</item>
        <item>A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step</item>
        <item>I failed in some subjects in exam, but my friend passed in all. Now he is an engineer in Microsoft and I am the owner of Microsoft</item>
        <item>You have to learn the rules of the game and then you have to play better than anyone else.</item>
        <item>A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new.</item>
        <item>Dream big, work hard.</item>
        <item>The only person you should try to be better than is the person you were yesterday.</item>
        <item>Be a hero, always say, I have no fear.</item>
        <item>You\'re already a successful person the things we take for granted someone else is praying for.</item>
        <item>If you can dream it. You can do it</item>
        <item>Everyday is a second change</item>
        <item>Be humble. Be hungry. And always be the hardest worker in the room</item>
        <item>Life is like riding a bicycle to keep your balance, you must keep moving.</item>
        <item>I will always choose a lazy person to do a difficult job because, he will find an easy way to do it.</item>
        <item>Enjoy the game and chase your dreams. Dreams do come true</item>
        <item>Don\'t waste your time with explanations. People only hear what they want to hear</item>
        <item>Do not pray for an easy life. pray for the strength to endure a difficult one</item>
        <item>I hated every minute of training. But I said, don\'t quit. Suffer now and love the rest of your life as a champion.</item>
        <item>First they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they fight you, then you win</item>
        <item>You miss 100% of the shots you don’t take.</item>
        <item>Life isn\’t about getting and having, it\’s about giving and being.</item>
        <item>Life is what happens to you while you\’re busy making other plans</item>
        <item>We become what we think about.</item>
        <item>The mind is everything. What you think you become</item>
        <item>Stop chasing the money and start chasing the passion.</item>
        <item>Everything has beauty, but not everyone can see.</item>
        <item>The best time to plant a tree was 20 years ago. The second best time is now.</item>
        <item>The best revenge is massive success</item>
        <item>Opportunities don\’t happen. You create them</item>
        <item>An unexamined life is not worth living</item>
        <item>Eighty percent of success is showing up.</item>
        <item>I\'m not a product of my circumstances. I\'m a product of my decisions</item>
        <item>Every child is an artist. The problem is how to remain an artist once he grows up.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>