<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="music">
        <item>Music is a moral law. It gives soul to the universe, wings to the mind, flight to the imagination, and charm and gaiety to life and to everything</item>
        <item>If music be the food of love, play on.</item>
        <item>Music doesn\'t lie. If there is something to be changed in this world, then it can only happen through music.</item>
        <item>Music is the movement of sound to reach the soul for the education of its virtue</item>
        <item>The world\'s most famous and popular language is music.</item>
        <item>Music is the strongest form of magic.</item>
        <item>Music in the soul can be heard by the universe.</item>
        <item>Music happens to be an art form that transcends language</item>
        <item>One good thing about music, when it hits you, you feel no pain</item>
        <item>Music expresses that which cannot be put into words and that which cannot remain silent.</item>
        <item>Music was my refuge. I could crawl into the space between the notes and curl my back to loneliness.</item>
        <item>Music is what feelings sound like. </item>
        <item>Music is the poetry of the air.</item>
        <item>Music is the art which is most nigh to tears and memory. </item>
        <item>Music is well said to be the speech of angels.</item>
        <item>Music is very spiritual, it has the power to bring people together.</item>
        <item>Music washes away from the soul the dust of everyday life.</item>
        <item>Music cleanses the understanding; inspires it, and lifts it into a realm which it would not reach if it were left to itself.   </item>
        <item>Music gives a soul to the universe, wings to the mind, flight to the imagination and life to everything</item>
        <item>Without music, life would be a mistake.</item>
        <item>Music is what tells us that the human race is greater than we realize.</item>
        <item>Music produces a kind of pleasure which human nature cannot do without</item>
        <item>Music is the universal language of mankind.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>