<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="sad">
        <item>In the book of life, the answers aren\'t in the back.</item>
        <item>If you see a friend without a smile; give him one of yours.</item>
        <item>Nobody deserves your tears, but whoever deserves them will not make you cry.</item>
        <item>All good things must come to an end, but all bad things can continue forever.</item>
        <item>The walls we build around us to keep sadness out also keeps out the joy.</item>
        <item>It\'s easy to cry when you realize that everyone you love will reject you or die.</item>
        <item>Good humor is the health of the soul, sadness its poison</item>
        <item>Smile, even if it\'s a sad smile, because sadder than a sad smile is the sadness of not knowing how to smile</item>
        <item>Anger, tears and sadness are only for those who have given up.</item>
        <item>Absolute silence leads to sadness. It is the image of death</item>
        <item>Sadness is but a wall between two gardens</item>
        <item>Sorrow is one of the vibrations that prove the fact of living</item>
        <item>There is no worse sorrow than remembering happiness in the day of sorrow</item>
        <item>When sorrows come, they come not single spies, but in battalions.</item>
        <item> Sadness is always the legacy of the past; regrets are pains of the memory.</item>
        <item>We gather strength from sadness and from pain Each time we die we learn to live again.</item>
        <item>Sorrow is like a precious treasure, shown only to friends.</item>
        <item>Tears are words the heart can\'t express.</item>
        <item>They that sow in tears shall reap in joy.</item>
        <item>Life is pleasant. Death is peaceful. It\'s the transition that\'s troublesome</item>
        <item>There is no greater sorrow than to recall in misery the time when we were happy.</item>
        <item>Hating people is like burning down your house to kill a rat.</item>
        <item>As a well-spent day brings happy sleep, so a life well spent brings happy death</item>
        <item> It is loneliness that makes the loudest noise. This is true of men as of dogs.</item>
        <item>Although the world is full of suffering, it is also full of the overcoming of it.</item>
        <item> I talk to God but the sky is empty.</item>
        <item>The absence of love is the most abject pain.</item>
        <item>I\’ll be okay is that what you want to say?</item>
        <item>The World is mad and the people are sad.</item>
        <item> But they all didn\’t see the little bit of sadness in me.</item>
        <item>Never put your happiness in someone else\’s hands.</item>
        <item>Be careful who you fall in love with,cause someone somewhere not approve.</item>
        <item>A feeling of sadness seemingly without a cause.</item>
        <item> I did everything right for someone that does everything wrong.</item>
        <item> I don\’t think you know what you are doing to me.</item>
        <item>You know my name not my story.</item>
        <item> Sometimes it takes losing something to realize what you\’ve had.</item>
        <item>Yesterday I was sad today i am happy yesterday i had a problem today i still have the same problem</item>
        <item> They don\’t love me,they know me when they need me. </item>
        <item> My tears are like anchors that sink my heart to the depths of the deepest ocean.</item>
        <item>Temporary happiness isn\’t worth long term pain.</item>
        <item>People walk away easily but they leave their memories with us forever.</item>
        <item> May it\’s not about the happy ending.May be it\’s about story.</item>
        <item> I was born with an enormous need for affection and a terrible need to give it.</item>
        <item> Did I change or did you just stop loving me.</item>
        <item>I am not worthy of being in love.</item>
        <item>Love is the person you think about during the sad songs.</item>
        <item>I wonder if you know what you are doing to me. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>