<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="sports">
        <item>Grab a tissue and several punching bags, it\'s about to get feisty in here.</item>
        <item>One man practicing sportsmanship is far better than 50 preaching it.</item>
        <item>Never give up, never give in, and when the upper hand is ours, may we have the ability to handle the win with the dignity that we absorbed the loss.</item>
        <item>Persistence can change failure into extraordinary achievement.</item>
        <item>Football doesn\'t build character, it reveals character.</item>
        <item>An athlete cannot run with money in his pockets. He must run with hope in his heart and dreams in his head.</item>
        <item>Age is no barrier. It\'s a limitation you put on your mind.</item>
        <item>Set your goals high, and don\'t stop till you get there.</item>
        <item>It’s not the will to win that matters—everyone has that. It’s the will to prepare to win that matters.</item>
        <item>The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person\'s determination.</item>
        <item>Make sure your worst enemy doesn\'t live between your own two ears.</item>
        <item>Champions keep playing until they get it right.</item>
        <item>If you fail to prepare, you\'re prepared to fail.</item>
        <item>What makes something special is not just what you have to gain, but what you feel there is to lose. </item>
        <item>A trophy carries dust. Memories last forever.</item>
        <item>The more difficult the victory, the greater the happiness in winning.</item>
        <item>One man can be a crucial ingredient on a team, but one man cannot make a team.</item>
        <item>Leadership, like coaching, is fighting for the hearts and souls of men and getting them to believe in you.</item>
        <item>You are never really playing an opponent. You are playing yourself, your own highest standards, and when you reach your limits, that is real joy.</item>
        <item>Always make a total effort, even when the odds are against you.</item>
        <item>You can motivate by fear, and you can motivate by reward. But both those methods are only temporary. The only lasting thing is self motivation.</item>
        <item>Without self-discipline, success is impossible, period.</item>
        <item>Do you know what my favorite part of the game is? The opportunity to play.</item>
        <item>Show me a guy who\'s afraid to look bad, and I\'ll show you a guy you can beat every time.</item>
        <item>If you have everything under control, you\'re not moving fast enough.</item>
        <item>Just keep going. Everybody gets better if they keep at it.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>