<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="success">
        <item>Action is the foundational key to all success</item>
        <item>Victory is sweetest when you\’ve known defeat</item>
        <item>Success is simple. Do what\’s right, the right way, at the right time</item>
        <item>Do not be embarrassed by your failures, learn from them and start again</item>
        <item>I cannot give you the formula for success, but I can give you the formula for failure which is: Try to please everybody</item>
        <item>Success is going from failure to failure without losing enthusiasm</item>
        <item>If you want to make an easy job seem mighty hard, just keep putting off doing it</item>
        <item>The successful man is the one who finds out what is the matter with his business before his competitors do.</item>
        <item>I attribute my success to this: I never gave or took any excuse</item>
        <item>You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have to play better than anyone else.</item>
        <item>Amateurs sit and wait for inspiration, the rest of us just get up and go to work</item>
        <item>Things may come to those who wait, but only the things left by those who hustle.</item>
        <item>Don\’t let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do.</item>
        <item>Life isn\’t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself.</item>
        <item>Not he who has much is rich, but he who gives much</item>
        <item>If the only tool you have is a hammer, you tend to see every problem as a nail.</item>
        <item>The distance between insanity and genius is measured only by success</item>
        <item>Never limit yourself because of others limited imagination; never limit others because of your own limited imagination</item>
        <item>To succeed in life, you need two things: ignorance and confidence</item>
        <item>The secret of success in life is for a man to be ready for his opportunity when it comes</item>
        <item>Don\’t wait. The time will never be just right</item>
        <item>After every difficulty, ask yourself two questions: \“What did I do right?\” and “What would I do differently?</item>
        <item>Don\’t brood. Get on with living and loving. You don\’t have forever.</item>
        <item>Doing the best at this moment puts you in the best place for the next moment</item>
        <item>Life\’s real failure is when you do not realize how close you were to success when you gave up</item>
        <item>If you\’re going through hell, keep going</item>
        <item>Be miserable. Or motivate yourself. Whatever has to be done, it\’s always your choice</item>
        <item>The first step toward success is taken when you refuse to be a captive of the environment in which you first find yourself</item>
        <item>For success, attitude is equally as important as ability</item>
        <item>Judge your success by what you had to give up in order to get it.</item>
        <item>Your work is discover your world and then with all your heart give yourself to it</item>
        <item>Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it.</item>
        <item>Success is largely a matter of holding on after others have let go</item>
        <item>Start where you are. Use what you have. Do what you can.</item>
        <item>Success seems to be connected with action. Successful people keep moving. They make mistakes, but they don\’t quit.</item>
        <item>Success is how high you bounce when you hit bottom</item>
        <item>Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try Again. Fail again. Fail better</item>
        <item>What seems to us as bitter trials are often blessings in disguise.</item>
        <item>Your attitude, not your aptitude, will determine your altitude</item>
        <item>The successful warrior is the average man, with laser-like focus</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>